[{"question":"Read each sentence to find out whether there is any grammatical error in it. The error, if any will be in one part of the sentence. The letter of that part is the answer. If there is no error, the answer is 4. (Ignore the errors of punctuation, if any).(solve as per the direction given above)","option1":"We discussed about the problem","option2":"on the eve of the examination","option3":"that I found it very easy to w","option4":"No error.","answer":1},{"question":"In the following questions choose the word which is the exact OPPOSITE of the given words.\nENORMOUS:","option1":"Soft","option2":"Soft","option3":"Tiny","option4":"Weak","answer":3},{"question":"choose the word which best expresses the meaning of the given word.\r\nCORPULENT:","option1":"Lean","option2":"Gaunt","option3":"Emaciated","option4":"Obese","answer":4},{"question":"Find the correctly spelt words.","option1":"Efficient","option2":"Treatmeant","option3":"Beterment","option4":"Employd","answer":1},{"question":"Pick out the most effective word(s) from the given words to fill in the blank to make the sentence meaningfully complete.\r\nFate smiles ...... those who untiringly grapple with stark realities of life.","option1":"with  \t","option2":"over  \t","option3":"on \t","option4":"round","answer":3},{"question":"In each question below, there is a sentence of which some parts have been jumbled up. Rearrange these parts which are labelled P, Q, R and S to produce the correct sentence. Choose the proper sequence.\r\nWhen he :\r\nP : \tdid not know\r\nQ : \the was nervous and\r\nR : \theard the hue and cry at midnight\r\nS : \twhat to do\r\nThe Proper sequence should be:","option1":"RQPS","option2":"QSPR","option3":"SQPR","option4":"PQRS","answer":1},{"question":"An incomplete statement (Stem) followed by fillers is given. Pick out the best one which can complete incomplete stem correctly and meaningfully.\r\nDespite his best efforts to conceal his anger ......","option1":"we could detect that he was ve","option2":"he failed to give us an impres","option3":"people came to know that he wa","option4":"he could succeed in doing it e","answer":3},{"question":"Some proverbs/idioms are given below together with their meanings. Choose the correct meaning of proverb/idiom, If there is no correct meaning given, E (i.e.) .None of these will be the answer. \r\n To make clean breast of","option1":"To gain prominence","option2":"To praise oneself","option3":"To confess without of reserve","option4":"None of these","answer":3},{"question":"Today most businessmen are very worried. To begin with, they are not used to competition.In the past they sold whatever ...(1)... produced at whatever prices they chose. But ...(2)... increasing competition, customers began to ...(3)... and choose. Imports suddenly became ...(4)... available and that too at cheaper ...(5)... ","option1":"it","option2":"he","option3":"they","option4":"we","answer":3},{"question":"Each question consist of two words which have a certain relationship to each other followed by four pairs of related words, Select the pair which has the same relationship.   \t\r\nDIVA:OPERA","option1":"producer:theatre","option2":"director:drama","option3":"conductor:bus","option4":"thespian:play","answer":4}]